<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>San Diego Real Estate Video Blog with John Stenberg</title>
    <description>Our mission at The Stenberg Real Estate Group is to be your best resource for San Diego real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The The Stenberg Real Estate Group, your professional San Diego Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 14:05:19 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 14:05:19 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Does Our Market Compare to Last Year?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wTQEtYQTi64?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;Here’s what’s been happening in the first six months of the 2021 market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In today’s market update, I’m going to compare the numbers in six ZIP codes from May 2021 to the same month last year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let’s start with median home prices:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Area code 91910 (Chula Vista): $735,000—up 27.2% over last year&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Area code 91911 (Chula Vista): $635,000—up 20% over last year&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Area code 91913 (Otay Ranch, Eastlake): $765,000—up 23% over last year&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Area code 91902 (Bonita): $908,000—up 17% over last year&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Area code 91914 (Rolling Hills Ranch): $935,000—up 16% over last year&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;South San Diego: $630,000—up 14% over last year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of all those ZIP codes, the area with the highest rate of appreciation is Bonita with over 43%. If you own an attached property in Bonita, now is a good time to sell, cash out, or do a 1031 exchange.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=These trends will likely continue for at least the next six months as home prices continue upward.%20http://localhost:4000/how-does-our-market-compare-to-last-year.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“These trends will likely continue for at least the next six months as home prices continue upward.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the next six months, prices are expected to inch upward as inventory remains low. Interest rates are likely going to stay the same, which is currently about 3.25%. In our current market, we’re also seeing more and more buyers backing out of transactions. Here are the four things they’re worried about most:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Buyer’s remorse.&lt;/strong&gt; In the heat of the moment, buyers are getting worried about overpaying for properties, so they go home to sleep on it and ultimately end up backing out of the deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Buyers don’t like a lot of repairs.&lt;/strong&gt; Many don’t mind paying top dollar for a great property, but they don’t like to have to deal with a lot of repairs. If you have a property as a seller, make sure it’s in good condition; if it isn’t, you can expect buyers to hit you up for repairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Appraisal issues.&lt;/strong&gt; If you don’t have an appraisal gap clause in your contract, the buyer can easily back out of the transaction if the property doesn’t appraise correctly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Poor decisions on the sellers’ part.&lt;/strong&gt; Many sellers aren’t vetting their buyers; they’re focused on getting the highest possible price, not on getting the best offer altogether.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These trends will likely continue for at least the next six months as home prices continue upward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking about buying or selling a home in today’s market, feel free to reach out to me. I’d love to sit down with you for a consultation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 13:38:59 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-does-our-market-compare-to-last-year.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-does-our-market-compare-to-last-year.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Thoughts on a Potential Housing Bubble</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/tqGKF2gXkYI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;Here’s why I don’t believe we’re in a housing bubble right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most common question I’ve been hearing lately is, “Are we in a housing bubble?” Today I’m going over a few reasons why we’re not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although there are some similarities between this market and the one we saw before the previous market crash, right now we simply have an issue with inventory that has been coming for many years. &lt;strong&gt;This is a completely different market from the last bubble and subsequent crash.&lt;/strong&gt; That was caused by bad loans, which aren’t around these days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Home inventory is so low that we have a 50-year low on building new construction homes. We are 3.8 million new homes behind schedule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Those bad loans from 2008 aren’t around today.%20http://localhost:4000/my-thoughts-on-a-potential-housing-bubble.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Those bad loans from 2008 aren’t around today.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re here in San Diego, we have a surplus of people moving here that’s further compounding our inventory issues. &lt;strong&gt;We have 24,000 people moving here each year, but we’re only building 12,000 new units.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another factor is that homeowners are staying in their properties longer and building up more equity. We aren’t seeing many defaults anymore, and homeowners have more equity than they ever have. 56% of homeowners have over 50% equity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of these reasons point to a much different market than a bubble. &lt;strong&gt;This is still a great market to be a home seller in, and low interest rates have made homes very affordable for buyers.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about the market or real estate in general, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 02:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/my-thoughts-on-a-potential-housing-bubble.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/my-thoughts-on-a-potential-housing-bubble.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Get an Offer Accepted in Today’s Market</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q1eCxUKDbvE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;Here are three tips for strengthening your offer in this competitive market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are three things that you must do when making an offer in today’s real estate market to increase your chances of getting that offer accepted:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Be educated.&lt;/strong&gt; Listen to your agent. Do extra research on home values in the neighborhood you’re choosing to buy into. Don’t look at the past 60 or 90 days. Look at the leading indicators (i.e., pending and closed sales).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Offer an appraisal gap clause.&lt;/strong&gt; If you make an offer of $525,000 on a home that’s listed at $500,000, you need to let the seller know that you’re willing to go up to that price even if the home’s appraisal comes in lower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Educate yourself on the market and pay close attention to leading indicators.%20http://localhost:4000/how-to-get-an-offer-accepted-in-todays-market.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Educate yourself on the market and pay close attention to leading indicators.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Offer a seller rent-back.&lt;/strong&gt; With our low inventory of homes, sellers are worried about finding their next home. Offering a rent-back upfront gives sellers peace of mind that they will have time to find a new home in this competitive home-buying market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus tip: Don’t give up!&lt;/strong&gt; We’re expecting home appreciation to hit 9% this year in San Diego. It’s really tough out there right now, but if you work with an experienced agent who knows the neighborhood you want to buy in, you’re in a much better position to win. And you will win if you stay patient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions for me, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 03:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-get-an-offer-accepted-in-todays-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-to-get-an-offer-accepted-in-todays-market.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3 Essential Tips for Selling a Rental Property</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/inmQnaZH6FI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;Here are my top tips for selling a San Diego rental property in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are three things you must do if you’re selling a rental property in 2021:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Start early.&lt;/strong&gt; If you’re thinking about selling in the summer, start preparing now. You need 60 to 90 days to get your home ready. Start working on your curb appeal, exterior photos, and notify the tenants of the situation (and have them sign the necessary paperwork).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Focus on pricing.&lt;/strong&gt; Right now, home prices are at an all-time high and they might go up another 9% this year. Even so, homes need to be priced properly based on their condition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Prepare the tenants and owner to sell in one day.&lt;/strong&gt; If you do the right marketing in advance, you’re going to be able to sell that rental property in just one weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus tip:&lt;/strong&gt; Give some type of incentive to a tenant for being cooperative. In today’s rent-control and COVID market, you want to assure your success by giving some type of cash incentive to the tenant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions for me about selling a rental property or real estate in general, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 02:18:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-essential-tips-for-selling-a-rental-property.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/3-essential-tips-for-selling-a-rental-property.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Latest San Diego Market Update</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fhr14KKmw7o?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here’s how our market is doing and where we believe it’s headed this year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s happening in the real estate market? I get asked this question almost daily, so today I’m sharing how our market’s doing and what we expect it to do throughout the year. With low interest rates, low inventory, and the pandemic, 2020 created the perfect seller’s market, but those rates also made a great buyer’s market. &lt;strong&gt;The 10-Year Treasury is pushing up interest rates,&lt;/strong&gt; and we’ll likely see 3.25% to 3.5% be the norm; we believe the 2% range is over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We have an inventory issue, and that’s why we’re seeing a frenzy of 20 to 40 offers on one property.%20http://localhost:4000/your-latest-san-diego-market-update.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We have an inventory issue, and that’s why we’re seeing a frenzy of 20 to 40 offers on one property.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2010, we had over 20,000 homes on the market, right after the foreclosure housing crisis. We currently have 2,200 houses on the market; we have an inventory issue, and that’s why we’re seeing a frenzy of 20 to 40 offers on one property. In the U.S., we’re short approximately 360,000 units each year in building for our growing population.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The median home price in South County is $635,000 and appreciated 24% year over year; in the metro area, it’s $666,000 and appreciated 9.6%; East County is $575,000 with 13% appreciation, and North County is at $800,000 with 12.7% appreciation. According to CoreLogic, a data provider for the real estate and mortgage industries, &lt;strong&gt;San Diego has seen 11% appreciation across the board from last year,&lt;/strong&gt; and they predict up to 9.6% more appreciation in 2021. We think we’ll see a roller coaster between March and May.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rates will increase a bit, causing buyers to feel the pressure to go out and buy a home. We also predict buyers will have a little more inventory to choose from because more homeowners are getting vaccinated, and they’ll feel more comfortable putting their houses up for sale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like more information, you can view &lt;em&gt;Mortgage News Daily’s&lt;/em&gt; article &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mortgagenewsdaily.com/03022021_corelogic_hpi.asp&quot;&gt;Home Price Appreciation Broke an 8-Year Record in January.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about the market or real estate in general, call or email us. We would love to be your real estate resource.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/your-latest-san-diego-market-update.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/your-latest-san-diego-market-update.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Due Diligence on a Physical Inspection</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/GSAStZs0kE4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you buy a home, there is a 17-day default clause in the contract that all of your inspections and investigations will be performed during. You’re also obligated to deal with requests for repairs if there are any discrepancies that you’re not satisfied with. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I would recommend that you get your inspection ordered right away after your offer is accepted.&lt;/strong&gt; Then, make sure you get all of the seller’s reports and disclosures before you start doing your inspections. Finally, you may want to go straight to a specialist if a home is older. They will give you estimates of what the repairs would cost so that you have the information to give to the seller. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=I recommend ordering an inspection right away.%20http://localhost:4000/due-diligence-on-a-physical-inspection.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“I recommend ordering an inspection right away.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Talk to your agent and determine whether a general or a specialty inspection is the right decision for the property you’re interested in.&lt;/strong&gt; If you have any questions for me in the meantime, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 01:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/due-diligence-on-a-physical-inspection.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/due-diligence-on-a-physical-inspection.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Our Coming Soon Program Helps You</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/UvXn339OgVk?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m proud to announce a great new service that our company is offering all of you. It’s our Compass Coming Soon program. We have hundreds of properties here that are not officially on the market, but are for sale nonetheless. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stenbergrealestate.com/&quot;&gt;Visit this&lt;/a&gt; site to see even more homes that are available in San Diego that you won’t see anywhere else. If you’ve been struggling to find a home, this may be the perfect place for you to look. To learn more about the program, watch my latest video.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 22:44:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-our-coming-soon-program-helps-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-our-coming-soon-program-helps-you.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Can the Compass Concierge Program Do for You?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ixpdBp-9Rww?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever been in a position to sell your home only to realize that you don’t have the money to make the upgrades and repairs you need to? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compass Concierge, our team’s newest marketing program, takes care of this problem for you. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Statistics say that when you stage your home and make all the necessary cosmetic repairs, you tend to sell for 5% to 20% more. Also, 83% of all buyer’s agents say that their buyers can better visualize themselves living in a home during a showing if the home’s been upgraded. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Compass Concierge helps you sell your home faster and for more money.%20http://localhost:4000/what-can-the-compass-concierge-program-do-for-you.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Compass Concierge helps you sell your home faster and for more money.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are numbers you can’t ignore, and Compass Concierge helps you sell your home faster and for more money by covering the cost of services to prepare your home for the market. Whether you need a new roof, carpet, A/C unit, etc., nothing is off the list. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best part about this program is that there are no hidden costs or upfront charges. You get billed at the close of escrow, and the vendors get paid before that. It’s a win-win situation for everyone involved. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To find out more about this program and to see if you can take advantage of it, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.compass.com/concierge/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;click on this link. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions, don’t hesitate to give me a call or shoot me an email. I’d love to speak with you.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 04:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-can-the-compass-concierge-program-do-for-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-can-the-compass-concierge-program-do-for-you.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Come Be a Part of Our Upcoming Padres Theme Nights</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/AXSwes7EGsk?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you probably already know, along with Compass, I’m a proud sponsor of the San Diego Padres at Petco Park this year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this in mind, I’m excited to bring something else to your attention: We’ll be hosting more than 40 theme nights at the ballpark this year, and you’re invited to attend any and all of them! I’ve written down my personal favorites, so feel free to contact me or visit our website for further information. Some of my favorites include: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Autism Awareness Night &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nurse’s Appreciation Weekend&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Winefest &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Party in the Park &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;80s Night—Party in the Park &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Margaritaville Night, for the Parrotheads who love margaritas and Jimmy Buffet   &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Beerfest &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bruce Lee Tribute Night, with a Bruce Lee t-shirt giveaway&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Star Wars Night, for all you Star Wars fanatics out there&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Filipino Night—my entire family will be attending this one&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We’ll be hosting more than 40 theme nights at the ballpark this year, and you’re invited to attend any and all of them!%20http://localhost:4000/come-be-a-part-of-our-upcoming-padres-theme-nights.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We’ll be hosting more than 40 theme nights at the ballpark this year, and you’re invited to attend any and all of them!”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information about all the theme nights that are just around the corner, feel free to reach out to me by phone at 619-869-3838 or by email at John.Stenberg@Compass.com. I hope to hear from you soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 10:22:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/come-be-a-part-of-our-upcoming-padres-theme-nights.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/come-be-a-part-of-our-upcoming-padres-theme-nights.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s Going on in Our San Diego Real Estate Market?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/QkkqoqgbThU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People ask me what’s happening in our market on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, it all depends on whether you’re looking to buy, sell, rent, or invest in a home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now, the median price of a San Diego home is $570,000. Interest rates are as low as 4%, which means it’s an incredible time to buy. In addition, homes are on the market for a mere 28 days before they’re sold. We still have a low level of inventory, meaning we’re in a seller’s market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We still have a low level of inventory, meaning we’re in a seller’s market.%20http://localhost:4000/whats-going-on-in-our-san-diego-real-estate-market.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We still have a low level of inventory, meaning we’re in a seller’s market.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to buy now, it’s a good idea to work with an agent who knows the market inside and out. If you want to sell, use a proven strategy in order to net top dollar on your sale. &lt;strong&gt;I’d be more than happy to help you with your real estate needs and answer any questions you may have.&lt;/strong&gt; In the meantime, I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 11:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-going-on-in-our-san-diego-real-estate-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/whats-going-on-in-our-san-diego-real-estate-market.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
